Guide to the Washington Square Park (New York, N.Y.) and Washington Square Area Image Collection, 1850-1990 NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001
New York University Archives
- Series II: Washington Square Area
  - East 8th Street (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Construction Workers Taking Lunch Break on Ledge, 1984; wsa_2_3_15; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 2, Folder 3, Item 15)
    - Construction Workers Taking Lunch Break on Ledge, undated; wsa_2_3_16; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 2, Folder 3, Item 16)
    - South Side of East 8th Street Looking West from University Place, undated; wsa_2_3_17; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 2, Folder 3, Item 17)
  - 5th Avenue (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - MacDougal Alley or Washington Mews, May 1949; wsa_2_4_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches; New York University. (Box 2, Folder 4, Item 1)
    - 5th Avenue between Washington Mews and Washington Square North, circa 1921; wsa_2_4_02; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches; Baeje (Box 2, Folder 4, Item 2)
      Washington Square Park (New York, N.Y.); Washington Square |z New York (State) |z New York.
    - One 5th Avenue, 1930; wsa_2_4_03; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches; Underhill, Irving (Box 2, Folder 4, Item 3)
    - West 8th Street South Looking East from MacDougal Street., April 1945; wsa_2_4_04; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches; New York University. (Box 2, Folder 4, Item 4)
    - Washington Square North and Washington Square West, Looking North towards West 8th Street, April 1945; wsa_2_4_05; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches; New York University. (Box 2, Folder 4, Item 5)
    - Washington Square North and 5th Avenue looking West, circa 1945; wsa_2_4_06; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 2, Folder 4, Item 6)
      Greenwich Village (New York, N.Y.); Washington Square Park (New York, N.Y.); Washington Square |z New York (State) |z New York.
    - West 8th Street and 5th Avenue, April 1945; wsa_2_4_07; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches; New York University. (Box 2, Folder 4, Item 7)
    - MacDougal Street, undated; wsa_2_4_08; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 2, Folder 4, Item 8)
    - Barnes and Noble Bookstore, undated; wsa_2_4_09; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 2, Folder 4, Item 9)
    - MacDougal Alley, May 1949; wsa_2_4_10; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches; New York University. (Box 2, Folder 4, Item 10)
    - 5th Avenue?, April 1945; wsa_2_4_11; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches; New York University. (Box 2, Folder 4, Item 11)
    - 5th Avenue?, April 1945; wsa_2_4_12; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches; New York University. (Box 2, Folder 4, Item 12)
    - MacDougal Alley or Washington Mews, May 1949; wsa_2_4_13; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches; New York University. (Box 2, Folder 4, Item 13)
    - MacDougal Alley, May 1949; wsa_2_4_14; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 2, Folder 4, Item 14)
      Duplicate of wsa_2_4_10
    - 5th Avenue or Broadway, undated; wsa_2_4_15; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 2, Folder 4, Item 15)
    - 5th Avenue or Broadway, undated; wsa_2_4_16; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 2, Folder 4, Item 16)
    - 5th Avenue Looking North from 8th Street, undated; wsa_2_4_17; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 2, Folder 4, Item 17)
    - 5th Avenue and West 8th Street, undated; wsa_2_4_18; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 2, Folder 4, Item 18)
    - Washington Square North and 5th Avenue looking West, circa 1945; wsa_2_4_19; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches; New York University. (Box 2, Folder 4, Item 19)
      Duplicate of wsa_2_4_06
    - Washington Square North and 5th Avenue, no date; wsa_2_4_20; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 2, Folder 4, Item 20)
    - Waverly Place, no date; wsa_2_4_21; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 2, Folder 4, Item 21)
    - 5th Avenue at West 8th Street, undated; wsa_2_4_22; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 2, Folder 4, Item 22)
    - Washington Square Park Looking North to 5th Avenue, undated; wsa_2_4_23; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 2, Folder 4, Item 23)
  - Films and Filming in NYU Area (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Filming of "No Small Affair" with Matthew Broderick and Martin Ritt, March 17, 1981; wsa_2_5_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches; Chin, Danny (Box 2, Folder 5, Item 1)
    - Filming of "Soup For One", March 13, 1981; wsa_2_5_02; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches; Katz, Ken (Box 2, Folder 5, Item 2)
    - Filming of "Four Friends", October 1980; wsa_2_5_03; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches; Chin, Danny (Box 2, Folder 5, Item 3)
    - Filming of "No Small Affair" with Matthew Broderick, March 17, 1981; wsa_2_5_04; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches; Chin, Danny (Box 2, Folder 5, Item 4)
    - Filming of "Soup For One", March 13, 1981; wsa_2_5_05; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches; Katz, Ken (Box 2, Folder 5, Item 5)
      Duplicate of wsa_2_5_16.
    - Still from the film "Children of the Corn", 1984; wsa_2_5_06; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches; New World Pictures (Firm). (Box 2, Folder 5, Item 6)
    - Still from the film "Children of the Corn", 1984; wsa_2_5_07; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches; New World Pictures (Firm). (Box 2, Folder 5, Item 7)
    - Still from the film "Children of the Corn", 1984; wsa_2_5_08; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches; New World Pictures (Firm). (Box 2, Folder 5, Item 8)
    - Still from the film "Children of the Corn", 1984; wsa_2_5_09; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches; New World Pictures (Firm). (Box 2, Folder 5, Item 9)
    - Still from the film "Children of the Corn", 1984; wsa_2_5_10; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches; New World Pictures (Firm). (Box 2, Folder 5, Item 10)
    - Still from the film "Children of the Corn", 1984; wsa_2_5_11; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches; New World Pictures (Firm). (Box 2, Folder 5, Item 11)
    - Still from "When The Mountains Tremble", undated; wsa_2_5_12; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches; Simon, Jean Marie (Box 2, Folder 5, Item 12)
    - Filming at night, undated; wsa_2_5_13; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 2, Folder 5, Item 13)
    - Filming of "Soup For One", March 13, 1981; wsa_2_5_14; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches; Katz, Ken (Box 2, Folder 5, Item 14)
    - Tisch Students Filming in Washington Square Park, October 1981; wsa_2_5_15; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches; Friedman, Mark (Box 2, Folder 5, Item 15)
    - Filming of "Soup For One", March 13, 1981; wsa_2_5_16; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches; Katz, Ken (Box 2, Folder 5, Item 16)
      Duplicate of wsa_2_5_06
    - Filming of "Soup For One", March 13, 1981; wsa_2_5_17; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches; Katz, Ken (Box 2, Folder 5, Item 17)
    - Film Student, Tisch School of the Arts, undated; wsa_2_5_18; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 2, Folder 5, Item 18)
    - Hollywood Junket, February 1982; wsa_2_5_19; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches; Katz, Ken (Box 2, Folder 5, Item 19)
    - Filming on Thompson Street, November 13, 1983; wsa_2_5_20; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches; Charry, Jonathan (Box 2, Folder 5, Item 20)
    - Filming of "No Small Affair", March 17, 1981; wsa_2_5_21; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches; Chin, Danny (Box 2, Folder 5, Item 21)
    - Filming of "Four Friends", October 1980; wsa_2_5_22; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches; Chin, Danny (Box 2, Folder 5, Item 22)
    - Filming of "Four Friends", October 1980; wsa_2_5_23; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches; Chin, Danny (Box 2, Folder 5, Item 23)
    - Filming of "Soup For One", March 13, 1981; wsa_2_5_24; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches; Katz, Ken (Box 2, Folder 5, Item 24)
    - Film Crew at Main Building, Washington Square East, October 1981; wsa_2_5_25; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 2, Folder 5, Item 25)
    - Filming of "Soup For One", March 13, 1981; wsa_2_5_26; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches; Katz, Ken (Box 2, Folder 5, Item 26)
    - Filming of "Soup for One", 1981; wsa_2_5_27; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches; Katz, Ken (Box 2, Folder 5, Item 27)
    - Filming of "Soup for One", 1981; wsa_2_5_28; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches; Katz, Ken (Box 2, Folder 5, Item 28)
    - Filming of "Soup for One", 1981; wsa_2_5_29; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches; Katz, Ken (Box 2, Folder 5, Item 29)
    - Filming, undated; wsa_2_5_30; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 2, Folder 5, Item 30)
    - Filming of "Soup for One", 1981; wsa_2_5_31; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches; Katz, Ken (Box 2, Folder 5, Item 31)
    - Filming of "Four Friends", 1980; wsa_2_5_32; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches; Chin, Danny (Box 2, Folder 5, Item 32)
    - Film Being Projected, undated; wsa_2_5_33; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 2, Folder 5, Item 33)
  - Fires, NYU and area (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Fire Alarm at Rubin Residence Hall (exterior), 1981; wsa_3_1_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches; Friedman, Mark (Box 4, Folder 1, Item 1)
    - Firemen, undated; wsa_3_1_02; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 4, Folder 1, Item 2)
    - Aftermath of Fire at Westside Pier, undated; wsa_3_1_03; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 4, Folder 1, Item 3)
    - Firefighter at Work in Silhouette, undated; wsa_3_1_04; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 4, Folder 1, Item 4)
    - Fire at Unidentified Building, undated; wsa_3_1_05; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 4, Folder 1, Item 5)
    - Aftermath of Fire at Waverly, 1984; wsa_3_1_06; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches; Charry, Jonathan (Box 4, Folder 1, Item 6)
    - Aftermath of Fire at Waverly, 1984; wsa_3_1_07; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches; Charry, Jonathan (Box 4, Folder 1, Item 7)
    - Aftermath of Fire at Waverly, 1984; wsa_3_1_08; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches; Charry, Jonathan (Box 4, Folder 1, Item 8)
    - Aftermath of Fire in Main Building, 1983; wsa_3_1_09; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches; Chait, Marc W. (Box 4, Folder 1, Item 9)
    - Joseph G. Fitzgerald, Assistant Director and Manager Protection Department, 1981; wsa_3_1_10; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches; Friedman, Mark (Box 4, Folder 1, Item 10)
    - Joseph G. Fitzgerald, Assistant Director and Manager Protection Department, 1981; wsa_3_1_11; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches; Friedman, Mark (Box 4, Folder 1, Item 11)
    - Aftermath of Fire at Wilentz's Books, undated; wsa_3_1_12; black-and-white print (photograph), 2 x 3 inches (Box 4, Folder 1, Item 12)
    - Firefighters, Westside Piers, undated; wsa_3_1_13; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 4, Folder 1, Item 13)
    - Silhouette of Fireman, Westside Piers, undated; wsa_3_1_14; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 4, Folder 1, Item 14)
    - Firefighters, Westside Piers, undated; wsa_3_1_15; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 4, Folder 1, Item 15)
    - Fireman, undated; wsa_3_1_16; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches; Shiotani, Ken (Box 4, Folder 1, Item 16)
    - Fire on Sullivan Street, 1983; wsa_3_1_17; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches; Charry, Jonathan (Box 4, Folder 1, Item 17)
    - Fire, Sixth Avenue, 1981; wsa_3_1_18; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches; Comer, Philippe (Box 4, Folder 1, Item 18)
    - Firefighters at Westside Piers, undated; wsa_3_1_19; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 4, Folder 1, Item 19)
    - Firefighters, undated; wsa_3_1_20; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 4, Folder 1, Item 20)
    - Firefighters at Westside Piers, undated; wsa_3_1_21; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 4, Folder 1, Item 21)
    - Firefighters at Westside Piers, undated; wsa_3_1_22; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 4, Folder 1, Item 22)
    - Fire, Bleecker Street, undated; wsa_3_1_23 (Box 4, Folder 1, Item 23)
    - Aftermath of Fire at Wilentz's Books (exterior), undated; wsa_3_1_24; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 4, Folder 1, Item 24)
  - Grace Church (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Grace Church (engraving), undated; wsa_3_2_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 4, Folder 2, Item 1)
  - Graffiti (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Graffito (Waverly): "Take Away Nancy's Little Gun and Give Her the Business End of It!", 1981; wsa_3_3_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches; Katz, Ken (Box 3, Folder 3, Item 1)
    - Graffiti on Number Seven Subway, 1980; wsa_3_3_02; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches; Nguyen, Andy (Box 3, Folder 3, Item 2)
    - Number Seven Subway - Car Interior, 1980; wsa_3_3_03; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches; Nguyen, Andy (Box 3, Folder 3, Item 3)
    - Graffiti on Number Seven Subway, 1980; wsa_3_3_04; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches; Nguyen, Andy (Box 3, Folder 3, Item 4)
    - Graffito in Stairwell, undated; wsa_3_3_05; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 3, Folder 3, Item 5)
    - Graffiti, 1984; wsa_3_3_06; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 3, Folder 3, Item 6)
    - Person Defacing Desk, undated; wsa_3_3_07; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 3, Folder 3, Item 7)
    - Person Defacing Desk, wsa_3_3_08; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 3, Folder 3, Item 8)
    - Graffito: "Join the Immoral Minority!", 1981; wsa_3_3_09; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches; Katz, Ken (Box 3, Folder 3, Item 9)
    - Graffiti: "NYU Diploma Please Take One" (toilet paper), undated; wsa_3_3_10; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 3, Folder 3, Item 10)
    - Graffiti: "NYU Diploma Please Take One" (toilet paper), undated; wsa_3_3_11; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches; Katz, Ken (Box 3, Folder 3, Item 11)
    - "Sit On It", undated; wsa_3_3_12; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 3, Folder 3, Item 12)
    - Graffiti at Houston and Bowery Streets (Keith Haring), circa 1980 - 1989; wsa_3_3_13; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 3, Folder 3, Item 13)
    - Graffiti at Houston and Bowery Streets (Keith Haring), circa 1980 - 1989; wsa_3_3_14; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 3, Folder 3, Item 14)
    - "Freedom is Qualitative and Quantitative" (Main Building), undated; wsa_3_3_15; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches; Nguyen, Andy (Box 3, Folder 3, Item 15)
    - "Smash the State. Anarchy. Smash Capital...", undated; wsa_3_3_16; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches; Nguyen, Andy (Box 3, Folder 3, Item 16)
  - Greene Street (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Corner of Greene Street and Washington Place, 1935; wsa_3_4_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 3, Folder 4, Item 1)
    - Greene Street, 1964; wsa_3_4_02; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches; Pellettieri, Luigi (Box 3, Folder 4, Item 2)
    - Greene Street Looking North From West 3rd Street, 1964; wsa_3_4_03; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches; Pellettieri, Luigi (Box 3, Folder 4, Item 3)
    - Greene Street, 1964; wsa_3_4_04; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches; Pellettieri, Luigi (Box 3, Folder 4, Item 4)
    - Greene and Waverly Streets Looking South, 1964; wsa_3_4_05; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches; Pellettieri, Luigi (Box 3, Folder 4, Item 5)
    - Eighth Street and University Place, Looking East, undated; wsa_3_4_06; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 3, Folder 4, Item 6)
    - Eighth Street Looking West From Greene Street, wsa_3_4_07; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 3, Folder 4, Item 7)
    - South Side of West 4th Street Looking West from Greene Street, undated; wsa_3_4_08; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 3, Folder 4, Item 8)
    - 262 Greene Street, 1969; wsa_3_4_09; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 3, Folder 4, Item 9)
    - Greene Street, 1964; wsa_3_4_10; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches; Pellettieri, Luigi (Box 3, Folder 4, Item 10)
    - Washington Place and Waverly Place, undated; wsa_3_4_11; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 3, Folder 4, Item 11)
    - Greene Street at Wooster, undated; wsa_3_4_12; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 3, Folder 4, Item 12)
    - East Building, Washington Place and Greene Street, undated; wsa_3_4_13; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches; Sihler, Henry J. (Box 3, Folder 4, Item 13)
    - Greene Street and Waverly, undated; wsa_3_4_14; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches; Sihler, Henry J. (Box 3, Folder 4, Item 14)
    - East Building, Washington Place and Greene, undated; wsa_3_4_15; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches; Sihler, Henry J. (Box 3, Folder 4, Item 15)
    - North Side of West 3rd Street Looking East From Wooster Street, undated; wsa_3_4_16 (Box 3, Folder 4, Item 16)
    - Workers, undated; wsa_3_4_17 (Box 3, Folder 4, Item 17)
    - Udell Graphic Center, undated; wsa_3_4_18; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 3, Folder 4, Item 18)
    - Tillis Luncheonette, 1965; wsa_3_4_19; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 3, Folder 4, Item 19)
    - Street Corner, undated; wsa_3_4_20; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches; Sihler, Henry J. (Box 3, Folder 4, Item 20)
    - Beatty Hatters Printing, undated; wsa_3_4_21; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches; Sihler, Henry J. (Box 3, Folder 4, Item 21)
  - Hebrew Union (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Hebrew Union College, undated; wsa_3_6_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches; Smith, Jeff (Box 3, Folder 6, Item 1)
    - Hebrew Union College, undated; wsa_3_6_02; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches; Smith, Jeff (Box 3, Folder 6, Item 2)
    - Ground-Breaking Ceremony at Hebrew Union College, undated; wsa_3_6_03; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 3, Folder 6, Item 3)
    - Construction of Hebrew Studies Center, 1978; wsa_3_6_04; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 3, Folder 6, Item 4)
  - "House of Genius" (61 Washington Square South), 1948 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - South Side of Washington Square South Looking East from Thompson Street, 1948; wsa_3_7_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 3, Folder 7, Item 1)
    - Genius Row, undated; wsa_3_7_02 (Box 3, Folder 7, Item 2)
  - Jefferson Market 6th Avenue and 9th street) (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Children Protesting Closing of Jefferson Market Library Closing, circa 1965 - 1975; wsa_3_8_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 5 inches (Box 3, Folder 8, Item 1)
    - Children Protesting Closing of Jefferson Market Library Closing, circa 1965 - 1975; wsa_3_8_02; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 5 inches (Box 3, Folder 8, Item 2)
    - Children Protesting Closing of Jefferson Market Library Closing, circa 1965 - 1975; wsa_3_8_03; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 5 inches (Box 3, Folder 8, Item 3)
    - Children Protesting Closing of Jefferson Market Library Closing, circa 1965 - 1975; wsa_3_8_04; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 5 inches (Box 3, Folder 8, Item 4)
    - Jefferson Market, Sixth Avenue, undated; wsa_3_8_05; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 5 inches (Box 3, Folder 8, Item 5)
    - People Gathering Signatures Against the Closing of the Jefferson Market Library, circa 1965 - 1975; wsa_3_8_06; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 5 inches (Box 3, Folder 8, Item 6)
    - Jefferson Market Police Court (engraving), 1878; wsa_3_8_07; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 3, Folder 8, Item 7)
  - Map (circa 1820-30), 1820-1839 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Map of Greenwich Village (engraving), 1822; wsa_3_9_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 3, Folder 9, Item 1)
  - MacDougal Street (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - North Side of MacDougal Alley Looking East From MacDougal Street, 1945; wsa_3_10_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 3, Folder 10, Item 1)
    - Washington Square South and MacDougal Street, 1962; wsa_3_10_02; Pellettieri, Luigi (Box 3, Folder 10, Item 2)
    - MacDougal Street and Washington Square South, undated; wsa_3_10_03; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches; Sihler, Henry J. (Box 3, Folder 10, Item 3)
    - West Side of Washington Square West Looking North from West 4th Street, 1947; wsa_3_10_04; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 3, Folder 10, Item 4)
    - MacDougal Street, Between Minetta Lane and West 3rd Street, undated; wsa_3_10_05; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 3, Folder 10, Item 5)
    - MacDougal Street South of West 3rd Street, undated; wsa_3_10_06; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches; Mal Gurian Associates. (Box 3, Folder 10, Item 6)
    - North Side of West 3rd Street Looking East from Sixth Avenue, undated; wsa_3_10_07; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 3, Folder 10, Item 7)
    - East Side of MacDougal Street Looking South from West 8th Street, 1947; wsa_3_10_08; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 3, Folder 10, Item 8)
    - North Side of West 3rd Street Looking West 8th from MacDougal Street, 1945; wsa_3_10_09; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 3, Folder 10, Item 9)
    - West Side of MacDougal Street Looking North from Minetta Lane, undated; wsa_3_10_10; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 3, Folder 10, Item 10)
    - MacDougal and West 3rd Street Looking West on West 3rd Street, undated; wsa_3_10_11; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 3, Folder 10, Item 11)
    - Calypso Club, MacDougal Street, undated; wsa_3_10_12; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 3, Folder 10, Item 12)
    - South Side of West 4th Street Looking East from Sixth Avenue, undated; wsa_3_10_13 (Box 3, Folder 10, Item 13)
    - South Side of West 8th Street Looking West from MacDougal Street, undated; wsa_3_10_14; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 3, Folder 10, Item 14)
    - West Side of MacDougal Street Looking South from West 8th Street, wsa_3_10_15; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 3, Folder 10, Item 15)
    - East Side of Sixth Avenue looking south from West 4th Street, circa 1940's-1950's; wsa_3_10_16; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 3, Folder 10, Item 16)
    - East side of Sixth Avenue Looking North from West 3rd Street, circa 1940's-1950's; wsa_3_10_17; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 3, Folder 10, Item 17)
    - West side of MacDougal Street looking north from West 3rd Street, 1945; wsa_3_10_18; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 3, Folder 10, Item 18)